burupo.com 2017-09-22

# The Burupo.com Privacy Policy - Boost up your Russian with Polina

When **you**   **use a form to  ask a question or to order a lesson** on the website, I ask you to fill in your name and email. This information I need to know to whom and to which address I should answer. The same principle works with Email Subscriptions.

When **you leave a comment to a post** , the website asks you to fill in your name and email. These fields are optional: you can skip them. Your comment will still be published.

I also use _**Google Analytics**_. You can learn more about the data collected by _Google Analytics_ [here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

I use all personal information for the purposes described in the paragraph 1.

And I never transmit personal data to any third party except in the following cases:

  * Emailing plugin [MailPoet](http://www.mailpoet.com/), which I use to automate my mailings.
  * _Google Analytics,_ which I use to analyze traffic to this website.
  * Situations, when disclosure is required by law.

All personal information is stored at the server of my hosting provider. And Google stores the data collected by Google Analytics.

I take all the reasonable precautions to protect personal data from any unauthorized use (for example: strong passwords, reliable hosting provider, regular antivirus checking).

You may also want to read [the Privacy policy of Google](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

If you have any questions related to this policy, don’t hesitate to ask me by email (polina@burupo.com) or in[ Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/burupo/).

**Published on June, 7th, 2017**
